#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/emidago (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Attention to Detail Confidentiality Microsoft Office

## Languages

English (Professional Working)
Filipino (Native or Bilingual)

## Certifications

Start Your Talent Insights Journey Assessment

Get Started with LinkedIn Learning Assessment

#### Honors-Awards

Proficiency in Humanities, Arts, and Social Sciences

# Emma A.

Freelancer | Part-time | Remote | WFH

Calabarzon, Philippines

## Summary

Have a Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology with an experience in Data Entry. Interested in Video and Photo Editing and in other media-related works and is willing to learn, can handle confidentiality, persevere and a detailed person.

## Experience

TELUS International AI Data Solutions

Freelancer

July 2023 - December 2023 (6 months)

Philippines

Freelance job where I participated in some projects related to Data Collection.

#### Remotasks

Freelance Tasker / Reviewer May 2021 - June 2021 (2 months)

Remote

DepEd Division Office Student Intern June 2011 - September 2011 (4 months) Sorsogon City, Bicol Region, Philippines

Pinoy Data Capture Inc.
Data Operator
August 2009 - November 2009 (4 months)
Makati, National Capital Region, Philippines

National Statistics Office of the Philippines Student Intern July 2008 - October 2008 (4 months) Sorsogon City, Bicol Region, Philippines

## Education

Computer Communication Development Institute

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information Technology · (2010 - 2013)

## **ACLC** College

Associate's degree, Computer Systems Design and Programming  $\cdot$  (June 2007 - April 2009)